A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - 67-966, Yonsei University, Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1967-1972 (Box 21, Folder 201)
  - 68-004, Yonsei University, Equipment-Radiology, 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 202)
  - 68-005, Yonsei University, Salary Subsidy-Physiology Department, 1968-1973 (Box 21, Folder 203)
  - 68-006, Yonsei University, Equipment-Genetics Laboratory, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 204)
  - 68-027, Yonsei University, Equipment-Cardiology, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 205)
  - 68-028, Yonsei University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1972 (Box 21, Folder 206)
  - 68-029, Yonsei University, Equipment-Biochemistry, General Correspondence & Original Orders, Overseas Medical Supply Company, Beckman Instruments, Inc., 1968-1969, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 207)
  - 68-030, Yonsei University, Equipment, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 208)
  - 69-060, Yonsei University, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 209)
  - 69-061 I, Yonsei University, Postgraduate Training Program, General Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 210)
  - 69-062, Yonsei University, Salary Subsidy-Biochemistry, General Correspondence, 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 211)
  - 69-063, Yonsei University, Research-Methodology Workshop, General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 212)
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1971 (Box 22, Folder 213-214)
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG 1: 019
    Oversized architectural drawings-Yonsei University, Medical School, Proposed East Medical Science Building #Y-X10 and #Y-X 11
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG1:020
    Oversized architectural drawing, Yonsei University, Medical School, Proposed East Medical Science Building, #Y-X9
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG1:021
    Oversized architectural drawing, Yonsei University, Medical School, Proposed East Medical Science Building, #Y-X8
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG1:022
    Oversized architectural drawings, 4-Yonsei University, Medical Center, Scheme VI
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG1:023
    Oversized architectural drawings, 2-Plan of Medical College Extension, First Floor and Second Floor
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG1:024
    Oversized architectural drawings, 4-Yonsei University, Medical School, Preliminary Study
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG1:025
    Oversized architectural drawings, 3-Yonsei University, Medical School, Scheme 4, SK1-SK3
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971; 2014:022, SG1:026
    Oversized architectural drawings, 2-Yonsei University, Medical School, #YX-6 and #YX-7
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971; 2014:022, SG1:027
    Oversized architectural drawings, 2-Yonsei University, Medical School, #YX-1 and #YX-2
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971; 2014:022, SG1:028
    Oversized architectural drawings, 3-Yonsei University, Medical School, Study for New Mediical Science Building, #Y-X3-#Y-X5
  - 69-093, Yonsei University, Medical Sciences Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971; 2014:022, SG1:029
    Oversized architectural drawings, 2-Yonsei University, Medical Library
  - 69-094, Yonsei University, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 215)
  - 69-095, Yonsei University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 216)
  - 70-144, Yonsei University, Building & Construction-Medical Sciences Building, 1969-1973, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 217)
  - 70-148, Yonsei University, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 218)
  - 70-149, Yonsei University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1975 (Box 23, Folder 219)
  - 70-150, Yonsei University, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 220)
  - 71-177, Yonsei University, Equipment-Central Research Laboratory, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 221)
  - 72-238 I, Yonsei University Medical College, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972, 1974-1975, 1977
  - 72-269 I, Yonsei University Medical College, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1975, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 223)
  - 73-302 I, Yonsei University Medical College, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973-1974, 1976, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 224)
  - 73-303 Yonsei University Medical College, Postgraduate Training, 1973-1978 (Box 23, Folder 225)
  - 73-304 I, Yonsei University Medical College, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973, 1976-1977, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 226)
  - 73-305 I, Yonsei University Medical College, Supplies & Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 227)
  - 74-334 I, Yonsei University Medical College, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1974, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 228)
  - 75-346, Yonsei University Medical College, Research Committee Reports, 1976, 1978-1989 (Box 24, Folder 229-230)
  - Yonsei University, College of Nursing, General Correspondence, Dean, 1973-1975, 1977-1979, 1981, 1983, 1986-1989, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 231)
  - 74-335, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Development Fund, 1974-1991, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 232)
  - 77-360, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Nursing Education, Training & Research, 1977-1996 (Box 24, Folder 233)
  - Seoul National University, Department of Nursing, General Correspondence, 1977, 1980, 1986, 1988-1990, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 234)
  - 77-359, Seoul National University, Department of Nursing, Nursing Education, Training & Research, 1977-1993 (Box 25, Folder 235-236)
  - 80-393, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Training Technical Personnel, 1980, 1982-1990, 1993, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 237)
  - 80-394, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, National Teacher Training Center, 1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1987, 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 238)
  - 80-386, Seoul National University, Endowment Fund for Library, 1980-1986, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 239)
  - 80-386, Seoul National University, Endowment Fund for Library, 1980-1986, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 239A)
    Restricted-Financial materials
  - 83-424, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for General Development, 1983-1985, 1987-1990, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 240)
  - 83-424, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for General Development, 1983-1985, 1987-1990, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 240A)
  - 85-435, Seoul National University, Supplemental Endowment-Staff Development, 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 241)
  - 85-435, Seoul National University, Supplemental Endowment-Staff Development, 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 241A)
  - 85-438, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Endowment for Educational Development, 1985-1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 242)
  - 85-438, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Endowment for Educational Development, 1985-1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 242A)
  - Seoul National University, School of Public Health, General Correspondence, Dean-Huh, Jong, 1972-1973, 1976, 1978-1980, 1982, 1984, 1987, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 243)
  - 78-370, Seoul National University, School of Public Health, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1977-1988 (Box 26, Folder 244)
  - 78-370, Seoul National University, School of Public Health, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1977-1988 (Box 26, Folder 244A)
    Restricted-Finanial materials
  - Seoul National University, Financial Reports/All China Medical Board Grants, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 246)
  - Seoul National University, Financial Reports/All China Medical Board Grants, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 246A)
    Restrcited-Financial materials
  - 71-178, Yonsei University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 247)
  - 71-206, Yonsei University, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 248)
  - 71-207, Yonsei University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 249)
  - 64-762-52, Yonsei University, Fellow, Cho, Kyu Chul, 1964-1965, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 250)
  - 58-429, Yonsei University, Fellow, Choi, Kum Dcuk, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 251)
  - 66-896-61, 68-022-3, Yonsei University, Fellow, Cho, Tae Kyung, 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 252)
  - 70-141-53, Yonsei University, Fellow, Hahn, Yoon Sun, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 253)
  - 61-591-3, 61-591-37, Yonsei University, Fellow, Hong, Joon Sik, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 254)
  - 60-541-16, Yonsei University, Fellow, Hong, Pill Whoon, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 255)
  - 58-429-35, Yonsei University, Fellow, Hwang, Tai Sik, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 256)
  - 62-647-22, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kang, Doo Hee, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 257)
  - 66-896-50, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kim, Chong Hwae, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 258)
  - 66-896-40, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kim, Choon Kyu, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 259)
  - 66-896-43, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kim, Il Soon, 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 260)
  - 65-864-44, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kim, Je Hyun, 1965, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 261)
  - 58-429-34, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kim, Myung Sun, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 262)
  - 69-086-24, 71-141-32, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kim, Won Joon, 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 263)
  - 69-086-3, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lee, Eun Sook, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 264)
  - 65-868-8, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lee, In Ja, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 265)
  - 69-086-32, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lee, Keun Tae, 1967-1971, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 266)
  - 65-834-26, 66-896-63, 67-938-29, 68-022-14, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lee, Kyoung Hea, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 267)
  - 58-429-36, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lee, Nam Zoo, 1959, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 268)
  - 64-647-8, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lee, Pyung Hyun, 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 269)
  - 70-141-5, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lee, Yoo Bock, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 270)
  - 63-694-4, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lew, Joon, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 271)
  - 61-591-36, Yonsei University, Fellow, Lim, Eui-Sun, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 272)
  - 62-647-41, Yonsei University, Fellow, Min, Kwang Sik, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 273)
  - 69-086-11, Yonsei University, Fellow, Min, Kwang Sik, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 274)
  - 66-896-22, Yonsei University, Fellow, Pak, Soo Yun, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 275)
  - 72-266-30, Yonsei University, Fellow, Park, Byeong Mun, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 276)
  - 62-647-23, 64-762-4, Yonsei University, Fellow, Shin, Tai Sun, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 277)
  - 60-541-38, Yonsei University, Fellow, Song, Chung Suk, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 278)
  - 64-762-21, Yonsei University, Fellow, Suh, Chung Sam, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 279)
  - 64-762-53, Yonsei University, Fellow, Woo, Tae Ha, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 280)
  - 68-022-50, Yonsei University, Fellow, Yang, Yong Tae, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 281)
  - 68-022-52, Yonsei University, Fellow, Yoon, Sei-Ok, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 282)
  - 68-022-13, Yonsei University, Fellow, Yun, Duk Jin, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 283)
  - 70-141-55, 72-266-30, Yonsei University, Fellow, Park, Chun Sik, 1971, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 284)
  - 72-266-30, Yonsei University, College of Medicine, Fellowship Grant, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 285)
  - 73-318 (12), 73-329 (1), Yonsei University, College of Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 286)
  - Yonsei University, College of Medicine, Individual/Dean, Yang, Jae Mo, General Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 28, Folder 287)
  - 70-141-49, 70-141-64, Yonsei University, Fellow, Oh, Yung Keun, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 288)
  - 63-676, 64-739, Yonsei University, Consultant, Curran, Jean A., 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 289)
  - 60-555, Yonsei University, Consultant, Curran, Jean A., 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 290-291)
  - 57-416, Yonsei University, Visiting Consultant, Firor, W. M., Medical Education, 1957-1958, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 292)
  - 71-203.31, 72-266-30, 78-373-70, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Fellow, Kim, Eui Sook, 1972-1973, 1978, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 293)
  - 73-239-2-15-16, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Fellowship Allocation, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 294)
  - 78-373-17, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Fellowships, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 295)
  - 73-322, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Nursing Scholarships, 1973-1981 (Box 29, Folder 296)
  - 72-240 I, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Nursing Research, 1972, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 297)
  - 72-239 I, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Faculty Salaries, 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 298)
  - 71-208 I, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Research, 1971, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 299)
  - 71-203-30, 72-266-30, Yonsei University, College of Nursing, Fellow, Oh, Ka-Sil, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 300)
  - 61-591-19, 62-647-52, 64-762-13, Yonsei University, Fellow, Kim, Young Joon, 1961-1965 (Box 29, Folder 301)
  - 59-474-39, 60-541-51, Yonsei University, School of Nursing, Fellow, Hong, Shin Young, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 302)
  - 71-179, Yonsei University, Visiting Consultant, Gault, Neal L., Jr., 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 303)
  - 69-118, Yonsei University, Consultant, Whiting Associates International, Architectural Consultants, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 304)
  - 68-025, Yonsei University, Visiting Professor, Hyun, Bong Hak, 1965, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 305)
  - 71-175, Yonsei University, Visiting Professor, Shideman, Frederick E., Overseas Medical Supply Company, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 306)
  - 71-232, Yonsei University, Visiting Professor, Sung, Joo Ho, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 307)
  - 66-873, Yonsei University, School of Nursing, Furnishings & Equipment, 1964, 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 308)
  - University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Dean, General Correspondence, 1973, 1975-1981, 1983-1986, 1988, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 309)
  - 79-381, University of Malaya, Medicine, Endowment Fund for Library, 1979-1980, 1982-1989, 1991-1992, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 310)
  - 77-364, University of Malaya, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1977-1988 (Box 30, Folder 311)
  - 78-374, University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Medical Research and Planning, 1978-1987 (Box 30, Folder 312)
  - 72-287 I, University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1976 (Box 30, Folder 313)
  - 73-306 I, University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 314)
  - University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, General Correspondence, Dean, Danaraj, Thamboo J., 1962-1975 (Box 30, Folder 315-316)
  - CM 320, University of Malaya, Singapore, Visiting Professor, Hoeppli, Reinhard, 1954, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 317)
  - 59-489, 60-522, University of Malaya, Singapore, Visiting Professor, Van Dyke, H. B., 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 318)
  - CM 302, University of Malaya, Singapore, Hoeppli, Reinhard, 1953-1960 (Box 31, Folder 319)
  - CM 249 & 280, University of Malaya, Singapore, Visiting Professor, Hoeppli, Reinhard, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 320)
  - CM 301, University of Malaya, Singapore, Visiting Professor, Anatomy (Originally-Pathology), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 321)
  - 59-518, University of Malaya, Singapore, Visiting Professor, Eiseman, Ben, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 322)
  - CM 249 &320, University of Malaya, Singapore, Visiting Professor, Hoeppli, Reinhard, 1954-1956 (Box 31, Folder 323)
  - CM 362-14, University of Malaya, Singapore, Fellow, Balasingham, Thillaiampalam, 1956-1959, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 324)
  - 60-541-8, University of Malaya, Singapore, Fellow, Dixon, Theodore F., 1960, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 325)
  - 60-541-9,University of Malaya, Singapore, Fellow, Lin, Robert C. Y., 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 326)
  - CM 259-17, University of Malaya, Singapore, Fellow, Sandosham, Arthur A., 1943, 1947, 1953, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 327)
  - 58-429-16, University of Malaya, Singapore, Fellow, Yeoh, Chim Seng, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 328)
  - 61-583, University of Malaya, Singapore, Equipment, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 329)
  - 61-620, University of Malaya, Singapore, Equipment-Instrument Room, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 330)
  - 60-548, University of Malaya, Singapore, Equipment-Cardiology, 1960-1964 (Box 31, Folder 331)
  - 60-564, University of Malaya, Singapore, Research-Parasitology, 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 332)
  - 58-465, University of Malaya, Singapore, Equipment & Supplies-Pharmacology, 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 333)
  - 60-532, University of Malaya, Singapore, Equipment-Biochemistry & Pharmacology, 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 334)
  - CM 351, University of Malaya, Singapore, Equipment-Pathology, 1955-1956, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 335)
  - 63-689, University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Student Laboratory Equipment, 1963-1965 (Box 32, Folder 336)
  - 64-757, University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Equipment-Animal House, 1964-1967 (Box 32, Folder 337)
  - 64-758, University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur, Equipment-Photography, 1964-1968 (Box 32, Folder 338)
  - 86-466, University of the Philippines, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1986-1993 (Box 32, Folder 339)
  - 86-466, University of the Philippines, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1986-1993 (Box 32, Folder 339A)
  - University of the East, Philippines, General Correspondence, 1982-1988, 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 340)
  - University of the Philippines, College of Nursing, General Correspondence, 1972-1973, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 341)
  - University of the Philippines, College of Nursing, General Correspondence, Dean, Aragon, Leonor M., 1959, 1970-1973, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 342)
  - 76-355, University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1976-1988, 1990-1993 (Box 32, Folder 343)
  - 77-365, University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Training & Health Manpower Development, 1977-1988 (Box 32, Folder 344)
  - 79-382, University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Library, 1979-1982, 1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 345)
  - 85-435, University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Supplemental Endowment-Staff Development, 1985, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 346)
  - 85-435, University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Supplemental Endowment-Staff Development, 1985, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 346A)
  - 76-354, University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1976-1988 (Box 33, Folder 347)
  - 75-343 (5), University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1978, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 348)
  - 82-414-9, University of the Philippines, Fellowships, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 349)
  - 80-385-8, University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 350)
  - University of the East, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 351)
  - University of the East, General-Incorporation Papers, Financial Reports, etc., 1960, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 352)
  - University of the East, General, Cuyeckeng, Jose, 1958-1960, 1962-1969 (Box 33, Folder 353)
  - 67-982, University of the East, Preceptor Program, Rural Medicine & Training, 1967-1972 (Box 34, Folder 354)
  - CM 362-11, 57-397-17, Silliman University, College of Nursing, Fellow, Torrontegui, Rosario, 1956, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 355)
  - 62-633, University of the East, Books, Journals, and Equipment, 1962-1963 (Box 34, Folder 356)
  - 62-673, University of the East, Supplies & Equipment, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 357)
  - 63-729, University of the East, Equipment, 1963-1967 (Box 34, Folder 358)
  - 64-791, University of the East, Equipment-Out-Patient Department, 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 359)
    2014:022, SG 1:030
  - 64-791, University of the East, Equipment-Out-Patient Department, 1964-1966; 2014:022, SG1:030
    over sized architectural drawing
  - 64-792, University of the East, Preceptor Program, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 360)
  - 65-821, University of the East, Equipment, 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 362)
  - 65-822, University of the East, Equipment-Animal Quarters, 1964-1972 (Box 34, Folder 362)
  - 66-890, University of the East, Equipment-Instrument Repair Shop, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 363)
  - 66-891, University of the East, Biochemistry-Renovation & Equipment, 1966-1969 (Box 34, Folder 364)
    2014:022, SG 1:031
  - 66-891, University of the East, Biochemistry-Renovation & Equipment, 1966-1969; 201:022, SG 1:031
    Oversized architectural drawing
  - 66-922, University of the East, Equipment-Blood Bank, 1966-1970 (Box 34, Folder 365)
  - 66-923, University of the East, Support-Basic Science Departments, 1966-1968 (Box 34, Folder 366)
  - 67-981, University of the East, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Order, 1966-1972 (Box 34, Folder 367)
  - 68-016, University of the East, Microbiology Department, 1967-1975 (Box 35, Folder 368)
  - 68-047, University of the East, Equipment-Biochemistry, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 369)
  - 68-048, University of the East, Equipment-Clinical Teaching, general Correspondence & Original Orders, 1967-1972 (Box 35, Folder 370)
  - 69-077, University of the East, Equipment-Pharmacology, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1972 (Box 35, Folder 371)
  - 70-162, University of the East, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, Local Purchasing Correspondence, 1969-1975 (Box 35, Folder 372)
  - 70-163, University of the East, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 35, Folder 373)
  - 68-022-53, 69-086-49, 69-086-56, University of the East, Fellow, Asperilla, Purita F., 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 374)
  - 65-834-6, University of the East, Fellow, Asperilla, Purita F., 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 375)
  - 63-694-14, University of the East, Fellow, Austria, Gonzalo F., 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 376)
  - 69-086-31, University of the East, Fellow, Baccay, Potenciano, 1967-1972 (Box 35, Folder 377)
  - 65-834-38, 66-896-58, University of the East, Fellow, Cuanang, Joven R., 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 378)
  - 64-762-20, University of the East, Fellow, Cuyegkeng, Jose, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 379)
  - 62-647-53, University of the East, Fellow, Decena, Lilita B., 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 380)
  - 67-938-21, University of the East, Fellow, Divinagracia, Romeo A., 1967 (Box 36, Folder 381)
  - 62-647-28, University of the East, Fellow, Dumlao, Evangelina Maceda, 1962-1963 (Box 36, Folder 382)
  - 71-203-29, University of the East, Fellow, Ezpeleta, Mariano L., Jr., 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 383)
  - 67-936-9, University of the East, Fellow, Foo-Canto, Lourdes Lai, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 384)
  - 65-834-13, University of the East, Fellow, Gutierrez, Erlinda G., 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 385)